<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Мото Станція - міні сто по обслуговуванню мотоциклів та велосипедів</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Мото Станція - міні сто по обслуговуванню мотоциклів та велосипедів</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>uk-ua</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Заміна сальників та пильників вилки мотоцикла у Києві</title><link>/service/replacing-fork-seals/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/service/replacing-fork-seals/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Помітили масляні кільця на перах вилки?&lt;/strong&gt; Це перша ознака того, що сальники вийшли з ладу. Ігнорування цієї проблеми призводить до потрапляння мастила на гальмівні диски, погіршення керованості та дорогого ремонту дзеркала вилки через потрапляння абразивного бруду всередину системи.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Синхронізація карбюраторів мотоцикла у Києві</title><link>/service/carburetor-synchronization/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/service/carburetor-synchronization/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ваш мотоцикл почав «троїти», погано тримає холості або «їсть» занадто багато пального?&lt;/strong&gt; Часто причина криється у розбалансуванні роботи карбюраторів. Синхронізація — це точне налаштування дросельних заслінок, щоб кожен циліндр отримував однакову кількість паливно-повітряної суміші.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Чищення ланцюга мотоцикла Київ</title><link>/service/cleaning-motorcycle-chains/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/service/cleaning-motorcycle-chains/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ланцюг — це «м&amp;rsquo;язи» вашого мотоцикла.&lt;/strong&gt; Брудний, сухий або перетягнутий ланцюг не лише прискорює знос зірок, а й забирає потужність двигуна та може стати причиною серйозної поломки в дорозі.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Search Result</title><link>/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2018 11:07:10 +0600</pubDate><guid>/search/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="hiim-linda-mccoy-specilized-in-blog-writing-and-collecting"&gt;Hi,I’m Linda McCoy Specilized In Blog Writing And Collecting&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Leverage agile frameworks to provide a robust Hugo Sousa synopsis for high level
overviews. Iterative approaches to corporate strategy foster collaborative thinking to
further the overall value proposition. Organically grow the holistic world view of
disruptive innovation via workplace diversity and empowerment.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="contact-me"&gt;Contact Me&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;iWriter comes with a built-in contact form that you can use with Netlify or the Formspree.
&lt;a href="https://docs.netlify.com/forms/usage-and-billing/#app"




 target="_blank"
 


&gt;Netlify&lt;/a&gt; allows for 100 submissions per month for free.
&lt;a href="https://formspree.io/plans"




 target="_blank"
 


&gt;Formspree&lt;/a&gt; provides up to 50 submissions per month for free.
You can also easily switch to another contact form service if you want.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Element</title><link>/element/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/element/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="elements"&gt;Elements&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A paragraph looks like this — Globally incubate standards compliant channels before scalable benefits. Quickly
disseminate superior deliverables whereas web-enabled applications. Quickly drive clicks-and-mortar
catalysts for change before vertical architectures. Credibly reintermediate backend ideas for cross-platform
models. Continually reintermediate integrated processes through technically sound intellectual capital.
Holistically foster superior methodologies. Check out &lt;a href="https://statichunt.com"




 target="_blank"
 


&gt;Statichunt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>